Hello everyone, welcome to all of you friends.
In this video we are going to see
ICICI Prudential AMC IPO, this company is going to be
listed tomorrow.
What kind of updates are seen coming before the listing
and
what kind of
momentum can you
see in this company according to the updates coming here, we are going to talk about them in detail in this video.
Watch the video till the end and subscribe to the channel for such daily IPO grey
market premium updates.
Also, the
link to the Telegram group has been given in the comments.  You
can also join there
for timely updates.  First of all,
we are talking about the news of ICICI
Pidential AMC LED, if we talk about buying here, then according to the
call given,
if we discuss, then the PL which is being
set here, the target of this company is
3000, here we are talking about the target.
Talking about the reason behind this, first of
all, what you have
received before the listing is the coverage here, the
rating of the bike has been given here by PL Capital, which is the recommendation.
In the rating of this bike, you have been given the
target of about 3000 companies.  Approximately
39% upside from the cut off price which was allocated here, that is ₹2165
which is the cut off price here,
expectation of 39% gain here, according to the recommendation of this company which
is a brokerage firm and the fund here,
your target is being
discussed here.
But if we talk about this company, then the
heavy subscription that has happened here and the
brand name that is being associated with this company,
you are seeing a very positive outcome here because the
promoters of ICICI Principal AMC LED company are
selling their stake here.  If we
talk about ICICI Bank, then the
promoters holding was 50% before PIP,
it will be near 52% in the coming time,
which is a good positive point that
seems to be emerging with this company here
and even now if we talk about this company, then let us
talk about the promoters' holding here,
combining both, the promoters of this company will still have
almost 90% holding here
and in this, the entire issue
size will be allocated here, in this issue size, if
you
talk about the performance here, talk about top performing
assets, then if you
talk about this company, then this
company has created a place for you.  At the same time, the overall liquidity of this company will be
a little
less.  Here, the opportunity to sell the shares which have been completely
allocated to the retailers will be given to you mostly by them. There will
not be any major fall here in the first half hour or one hour tomorrow.  So the opportunity to sell the shares will
not be seen by them here.  Due to which
upside potential can be seen in this company.
Well,
if you are looking at this company for the long term, then on
11th of this, 1 crore 39573
equity shares worth up to Rs 321 crore have been
allotted here, the anchor investor will get the
opportunity to sell 50% of its shares on 16th of January.  The
opportunity to sell the remaining 50% shares is available here on 17th
March.  So these two dates are going to be
important dates for you in the coming time.
If we
talk about this, then the shares allotted to Kawaibi are
14.50% of the total issue size.  In
which
we have already discussed about the anchor investors
that shares worth approximately Rs 3000 crores have been
allocated to the anchor investors.
Whose lock in period time will be
after 30 days and after 90 days.
Talking about small HNIs, the
shares that will be allocated to you will be up to
14% and up to 14.25% shares have been allocated.
Talking about retailers,
approximately 33-33.25%
shares have been allocated to you.  And if we
talk about the share holders category, then
approximately 5% of the total has been
allocated to this size share holders category.
In the shares allotted to retailers,
you can see approximately how many
lakh retailers have been allotted in this IPO.
So approximately 273920
retailers have been allotted here in this IPO.  Let us
talk about the reason behind this allocation.  So first of all, in the first one
and a half hour, there is no
selling pressure of any kind from the retailers.
So, the
possibility of this company moving in the direction that is being talked about by the brokers here will remain
here.  Well, we are planning to play this momentum.  So,
we will discuss further how one should plan to hold or continue here with stop loss.
But right now the grey market premium of this company is
seen being traded at a record premium as per
its grey market premium SH report.  The
grey market premium of this company is
seen trading here around ₹490 485.
Currently the grey market premium of this company is
trading at ₹485.   If we
add ₹485 to ₹2165, then if we
talk about the listing price, it
seems to be coming out to be ₹2910.  If we talk about the
chances of getting listing gains on one lot, then there is a
chance of getting listing gains of around 22.5%.
Around 2900 IPOs are seen giving
you listing gains per lot in the coming time.
If you have been lucky and have
applied in any of the categories Big NI and Small NI and have got allotment, then
you would have seen allocation of up to Rs 2 lakh.
Due to which the
chances of getting allotment in this IPO seem to be
around Rs 4,000 as per the grey market premium.
By the way,
in which category in this IPO, how many lots did
you apply for, now you
can tell by commenting whether you have got allotment in this IPO.  Further, if you look at this company
from the point of view of listing gain, then
if you had applied only then you can take
whatever listing gain you are getting.
Otherwise, if you had
applied from the point of view of listing gain
but are
planning to hold here, then the plan to
hold here with a stop loss
can be made tomorrow at the low formed here in the first half hour. After that, when
Monday opens, let's
talk about the Friday low here, so
Monday's stop loss will be there.
Monday's low will be there. Planning can be done to
work with a stop loss for Tuesday's here.
So in this
way, you will have to strictly follow the stop loss here
because if there is any kind of
decline in the market, then you will have to
expect a correction here because you will see a
decline in any panic. If we talk about retailers there, then a
slight decline in participation can be
clearly seen and those who had
applied in this IPO only for the long
term, then the company looks excellent for the long term. The
company will be
seen doing good work in this work in the times to come.  In the
coming time, the way
financial
education is increasing here and the way per
capita income will increase in India, in the same way the
demands for you people will
increase in this sector, due to which this company is going to
get very good benefits in the coming time because if we talk about the brand of this company, it is a
company associated with the ICIC group,
due to which this company is also getting benefits.
Also, if we talk about listing gains, the
company seems to be giving very good listing
gains here.
What should be done if allotment is received?   If
you ask me personally, I am
looking at the allotment I have received here as per the plan of holding it here for about 2 to 3 days.  If we
talk about the target of this company for two to three days and it
tries to go above 3000
or goes around 2900 or above, then there will be a
plan to sell there.  Otherwise, if we
talk about this company, then
in the coming time,
this company is listed here around 2500, above 2500, around
26, 2700, there
is a plan to hold it here with a stop loss around 2500.  What do you do if you don't get personal allotment
?  So, if we talk about the first half hour, the
low that will be formed between 10 to 10:30, the planning of buying that low is done here with a stop loss
and the planning of holding it here with that stop loss could have been done
here.
Well, talking about this company, if there is any
further change in the grey market premium here in the morning,
then the
update will reach you people through video.  Whatever
doubt you have, you can ask by commenting.   I
hope all the information is useful for you, so
like the video and subscribe to the channel
and you will
get the link of the Telegram group in the comments.  You
must join there so that you will keep getting
all the updates on time and by the way,
what are your plans,
how can you tell them so that you can get an
overview, if you find any
other points interesting then
we will
discuss them in detail in tomorrow morning's video.  See you
in a new informative video, till then Jai
Hind Jai Bharat.